Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world
believing that surely someday.
We just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up, way up high.
Always step up.
If waves are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up.
Our wishes, they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
We drift on riding the waves.
Towards another shore day by day.
There are many meetings, many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember the pain within.
I'll keep it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly.
But I won't surrender.
This freedom I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up, way up high.
Always step up, if brains
are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up, our wishes,
they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
Hands up.
Something definitely isn't right.
I don't understand what's going on?
Why don't I see any idiot G-5
marines at the main entrance?
We should be looking at a pile of
solidified bodies, but nothing.
I can't prove the power of my land
of the dead without those corpses.
And if we don't have their bodies,
how can we be sure the Straw
Hat's law and smoker are dead?
What do you think, Vergo?
There's one thing we can be sure of.
Whatever happened, Straw Hat and
the others are not in that cage.
Huh?
They got free?
And why would you think that?
The Navy G-5 is nothing but
a bunch of useless meatheads.
I seriously doubt they will be able
to escape from the gas on their own.
Straw Hat and the rest escaped the cage
and helped the G-5 Marines as well.
They broke out impossible!
Master!
What's the matter?
It's Straw Hat, the Navy, everybody!
They're here, they're inside!
They got away from the poison gas
and they're in Building A now!
They're all about to advance further
into the laboratory they're here.
How is that even possible?
They shouldn't have been
able to get out of that cage,
let alone make it through
the laboratory door.
How did they get inside?
We don't know, sir.
More than anything, I don't like
that laws are the loose now,
depending on what he intends.
I may need to take care of him personally.
They're closing in! Master,
the Straw Hats and Marines
broke through our defenses
and are trying to push through
the lab toward the passage.
What's on, Luis?
That Master guy really
makes my skin crawl.
But at least I know the
others are okay now.
Who gave me this note?
What does it mean?
Were they telling me that Luffy and the
others could make it out on their own?
Now that I know the formula for the drug
and have the sedatives, I can help them.
I have no idea which way to go!
Tell me what my men are doing about this
troops have mobilized
against them in building
a the main unit They're posted at the back
of building B preparing
to make a stand sir
We know what they're after
escape away off the island
And that means we know
where they're heading.
They'll make a beeline for
building our and gate 66
No, no we stop them before they get close
Close the gate between the two
buildings and isolate building A.
After that, use the experiment
cannon and let in land of the dead.
Sir, if we do that, we'll be
leaving our own guards to die.
You will do as I say!
And place a surveillance nail, too!
Do you hear me? But... I...
Master...
For the Broker's benefit, we need
to restart this little experiment.
I have yet to satisfactorily
demonstrate my scientific mastery
What do you plan to do, Vergo?
Only a bunch of idiots will fall
for the trap you're setting up.
You're not the only one who would lose
face if we let Law and Smoker get away.
I've got a stake in this too.
I can't trust you to handle it.
I'll cut down whoever
and whatever I need to.
That's strange.
I can't find my sword.
Likely because you're
not a swordsman, oh yeah,
that's right, forgot that for a moment.
Still, I'll strike them
down every last one of them.
Do your worst, Straw Hat.
You won't get through me.
I'm one of building B's
gatekeepers in my pirate days.
I was called run the machete.
I served the master,
and you are his enemy.
So you're dead.
Don't look like animal legs to me.
What the hell kind of Century are you?
You're freaky! Move!
Spider!
Get out of my way!
Hey, Law, what's the siren?
It's a warning.
The gate in this building
is about to close,
cutting off the only
passage to Building B,
boxing us in.
Caesar.
What did you think?
Did he make it easy?
Your men better get moving, or
else they're not making it out.
I don't know what Law meant when he said
we only had two hours to get out of here.
But I do know we're not going
to let you get away, Straw Hats.
You've got nowhere to run.
Back down.
Get out of our way! Ha!
Hot!
Cool!
Yeah!
That's our boys!
Way to go!
Thanks for the ride, Brownbeard.
We owe you one. Sure thing.
I'm happy to help.
Although, I am curious why
you brought the dragon along.
Well,
our original plan was to get away from
the poison gas by flying on his back
but he never even got off the ground he
can't fly now because he's been injected
with sedatives even so it would have been
a better idea to leave him outside and
here he could do a lot of damage he's
dangerous really he's kind of cute though
this might be our only chance
let's take the stars down
now I thought I told you to
get out of our way huh but
captain why well hello copycat
a captain now huh what's
wrong don't want to fight me
no get the hell out of here stop
g5 we don't have the time to
be fighting right now head
for the back passage immediately
the only way out of this
building is about to be
sealed we need to get out now
caesar's ordered the gate closed
he's trying to fence us in
this is our chance to escape if
we don't make it out we'll be
stuck on punk hazard move faster
we die quick let's get moving
you all heard the captain if we
don't do as she says we're dead
come on let's go straight for
the gate don't stop for anything
Well, that's taken care of.
Hey, where'd you run off to?
You're back!
Yes.
Luffy asked me to do a
little favor for him.
You heard her, right, the Navy captain?
Pick up the pace, brownie!
We need to get out of here now!
That's impossible.
I can't go any faster.
I'm sick to death of all this running!
What, you tired? No!
I'm not a samurai, so I
have no problem saying it!
I'm tired!
Look!
What the hell's Brownbeard
doing helping out those pirates?
That bastard!
How can he even think
of betraying the master?
He's a traitor to the great savior!
We'll figure it out later!
For now we need to hurry!
Come on, Chief Five!
We need to move faster!
It's gonna close any minute!
Come on, come on!
Experiment cannons, stand by!
Target!
Third laboratory!
After wall of Building A!
Two walls been breached!
Hey, wait! That means...
You've got to be kidding me!
Run! Run!
Run!
Reach!
Almost there now!
Help me!
Just reach!
It'll close any second now!
Anyone left on this side will be a goner!
Hey, we're through.
Yes, we are.
Just barely.
Hey, Captain just came
flying in through the gate.
Glad you're safe.
But how did you get here?
Move out of my way.
There are still Marines out there.
I'm sorry.
It's way too dangerous.
The gate is almost close now!
I can't just leave them behind!
Let go of me!
They're still out there!
I have to help them!
You can't go out there!
You'll never make it!
I have to protect them!
No!
I have to save them!
Smoker told me!
He told me to look out for the men!
No, Captain!
It's too late!
There isn't any time!
Excellent, Marines!
Our Captain is safe!
You've done the Navy proud!
Thank you!
We'll take it from here!
Thou scum, I can't believe
so many of them survived.
The rest of you are mine.
I can't believe he
compromised his own land.
He must really want us all dead.
Hey, can't you run any faster?
Are you kidding me?
When did you all get on my back?
Jeez, it's getting too heavy.
You've got to forgive us, Brownbeard.
Just power through it.
I'm afraid we've got no other choice.
We don't? Why not?
We've been running all day, and now we
don't want to that's an awful reason.
Get off of my back.
Good sir!
Your name is brownbeard correct?
It pains me to ask this.
But my son is being held captive and I
need to rescue him as soon as possible.
However, I need your help because
I am simply too tired to run.
You're all fools!
Get off me, damn it!
It's actually starting to feel kind of
stuffy in this lab with this heavy coat on.
Here!
You can hang it with mine!
Hey, my back's not allowed.
If you're not hurt, get
down and run for yourselves.
I mean it!
I'm feeling a bit hungry.
A summoner eye is trained to
endure the pains of hunger.
Brownbeard?
Do you have any snacks stored back here?
Shut up, idiot!
As soon as we get back to the
post where my men are stationed,
I'm bucking you all off
and going my own way!
Snap out of it!
We've got to move!
We've got to warn people
about the deadly crap
this scum sucker's been
making on this island!
Yeah, we can't let them unleash
that stuff on the world!
We need to go!
We've got to report all
this to Navy HQ now!
If none of us make it
off Punk Hazard alive,
then all those guys who sacrificed
themselves to save you died for squat!
Yes, of course.
Let's move out!
What's making that weird noise?
Hey, there's something
in the dark up there.
What the hell?
It's a damn monster! That thing!
I saw it get inside the
lab with a Straw Hat crew.
No one ever told me lizards can fly.
They can't, and we're
not looking at a lizard.
I heard that there were dragons on
this island, but I didn't believe it.
They're more than just legend. Dr.
Vegapunk genetically engineered them
to protect Punk Hazard from outsiders.
It's scary.
It looked so much nicer
when we saw it earlier.
Here it comes!
It's a dark bullet!
It's chewing through solid steel!
Think of what those jaws would do to us!
Everyone, come on!
To Building B!
It flies, breathes fire, and eats steel!
How are we ever gonna beat this thing?
What the?
It's flying off! Where's it going?
It looked like something freaked it out.
Yeah, I got a look at Captain Tashigi.
Captain Tashigi, we're saved at last!
The big guns have arrived
to provide us some backup!
We got two Vice-Admirals on our side now!
I can't!
Vergo!
Vice Admiral Smokey and Vergo, the
G5 is finally ready to kick some ass!
Ain't no one gonna stop us now!
Oh, no. Hell, yeah!
Caesar's going down!
Run, everyone.
Run, now!
Vice Admiral Vergo, did those soldiers
do something wrong? Even if they did,
I'm all for punishment and everything,
but your finger pistol might kill them.
Welcome to G5.
Your reputation precedes
you, Commodore Smoker.
Pleasure to meet you.
You should know the soldiers of G5.
Well, they're a bit crude and simple.
But if you give them a chance,
you'll find they're not as bad
as people make them out to be.
In fact, they're some of the
most loyal men you'll ever meet.
Where's Vice Admiral Brook? Not here.
Where did he go?
Don't get worked up.
See, the Vice Admiral has to take leave
to visit home every once in a while.
How dare you!
Marines are supposed to help people!
I'm sorry, madam.
See, these men, I'm responsible for
their failure. Yeah? Then prove it.
Take some real responsibility
and fix my damn house.
Careful now!
Yeah, better watch your mouth, lady.
I agree with you, and I promise you that
your home will be fixed, whatever it takes.
Excuse me, sir.
Vice Admiral, about that child abduction
report from the other day. Oh, yes.
I ordered some men to look into it.
Seems as though it was an accident at sea.
Another false report.
Why would they...
It's difficult for any parent to
accept the death of their child.
But calling it an abduction gives
them some hope they're still alive.
You'll understand yourself
someday when you become a mother.
So that's really all there is to it.
Yes, that's all there is to it.
Everyone get back!
Run for your lives!
He's not the man you think he is!
Listen to me!
He's been working against -
Captain, no!
Captain!
This guy's an imposter!
The real Vergo would never attack
his own soldiers like this!
That's right, it's a disguise!
Or a Devil Fruit power! You bastard!
How dare you pretend to
be Vice Admiral Vergo!
The Vice Admiral Usgeist, no!
He's a man of honor who
always stands up for us!
Even if we're a bunch of misfits,
and he believes in justice,
there's no way you're him!
You damn Fight!
Let's kick his ass backwards! E-haw!
My words are frozen in my throat.
Smoker, anyone...
Please, you have to stop this.
I hear a lady. Who is that?
In need of my help!
Ain't that guy a Straw Hat?
Why is a pirate helping us?
I heard the heartbreaking
sound of a woman's tears.
Why do you think Sanji took
off in a mad dash like that?
I felt the presence of
someone dangerous creeping in.
He must have gone after them.
He'll catch them.
Wait, something's coming this way.
What now?
That's the dragon we
didn't ride here on. Is it?
He looks different somehow.
Look in his eyes.
The dragons are pretty savage by nature.
The only way to control the beast
is pump them full of sedatives.
Smaller ones like him are the
newer, more advanced models.
So he's even faster and
tougher than the others.
I'm going to rearrange Caesar's face.
Where are you going?
I'm going to straighten
out Vergo with my fists.
That's cool with me.
He's not with Caesar, is he?
Probably is.
Try to stay out of my way.
Wait, you bastard!
Stay away from Caesar!
Look at this.
What the hell does Vergo think he's doing?
I made it clear those G5
guys are my test subjects.
that idiots, not supposed to kill them,
land of the dead is what a
damn waste I have no choice.
Close the doors and seal off
the passage ahead of them
and then open up the other
gates to let the gas in.
Sure, but do you want me to do that?
With Vergo still inside, just do it.
He shouldn't have gone rogue
on me; it's his own fault.
We're almost at the biscuit room.
It's that way.
Let's keep moving.
You ready?
Are you serious?
Give me a sec.
Jeez, I was running so fast my
feet let the damn floor on fire.
You think that's easy?
I'm not like you.
I can't just go flying on a smoke cloud.
Are you ready now?
I just told you to wait.
I'll tell you when I'm ready, okay?
I'm starting to catch my breath.
Hey, did you hear me say I was ready?
Listen up.
There goes mine.
Stay back.
Yeah, I got it.
And you keep away from Caesar.
I'm the only one taking down that jerk.
Guess I'm up first. Fine.
Huh?
You're not getting away now!
These are secure!